[Music]
Hello everyone. If you're working with
feature management in Business Central,
we have got some exciting news for you.
We have just added automation API
support to make handling features easier
and more efficient. Here's what you can
do. You can invoke a get request to get
a list of all the available features and
their current status.
To activate a feature, we can start for
example with the first available feature
advanced tell me and we can activate
this feature
by invoking the activate bound action.
Once we invoke it, you can issue again
another get request to verify that the
feature has been enabled and activated
for all users.
You could also deactivate the feature by
invoking the deactivate bound action.
And once again, if you invoke another
get request, you will see that the
feature now is deactivated
in feature management.
It's fast, it's clean, it saves you
valuable time. Thank you for watching.